

MAXIM SVILYONOK

Middle Front-end developer

Date of Birth: 12/05/1988 Location: Belarus, Minsk

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Languages and technologies:
 - HTML, CSS/SCSS (BEM),
 - JS, TypeScript, NodeJS
- Frameworks and Libraries:
 - Angular, React/Redux, Next.js
- Tools:
 - GIT, Webpack, VS Code, Figma

CONTACT

Mobile: +375 (29) 229-96-75

E-mail: mlalx@tut.by

Telegram: https://t.me/BlackPanteraAga

LinkedIn: max-svilyonok

GitHub: https://github.com/Max-Sv

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATION

I've been doing front-end development for several years. During this time, I tried a lot of tools and frameworks.

I have successfully completed several projects. This experience gave me an understanding that web development is the right choice.

At the moment, I'm keen on backend development. I think within a year I will be able to expand my specialization and become a full-stack developer.

Front-end development experience over 2.5 years, of which 2 - commercial Development.

Experience with Angular 8-9 for about ~ 2 years.

Experience with React more a year.

I have experience in programming in object-oriented languages with strict typing (C/C++/C#).

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

- Projects and features development
- Tasks review and estimations
- Code review skills
- Communication with the customer

LANGUAGES

- English Intermediate
- Russian Native Speaker
- Belarussian Native Speaker

EDUCATION

BELARUSIAN NATIONAL TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY

INFORMATION TECHNOLOGIES AND ROBOTICS FACULTY

BELARUSIAN NATIONAL TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY

2018 – 2022

INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE OF DISTANCE EDUCATION "Information Systems and Technologies" Department

1

PROJECTS

THE MONITORING SYSTEM OF THE SUPPORTING STRUCT	
Company:	ООО «Сэнсэ Мониторинг»
Company Location:	Belarus, Minsk
Project Industry:	Monitoring of Building Structures
Project Web Site:	sensom.online
Web Site:	sensom.by
Description	The building on load-bearing beams has laser sensors.
	Sensors send data to the server every 30 minutes.
	Task: To allow you to see and evaluate the current load on the roof.
	General requirements:
	The user is logged in. The user has one of five roles.
	The administrator can draw and edit the roof diagram, edit and create objects and users.
	The owner can edit user data. The engineer can edit the sensor data.
	All users can see the data of the sensors in the diagram of the roof and using a chart.
Position:	Front-end developer
Overall Team Size:	1 front-end developer, 1 full-stack developer, 1 QA engineer, 1 designer, 1 manager
Tools & Technologies:	Angular 8-9(Angular Material, Chart.js, Snap.svg), Node.js (Express, Loopback3, Mongoose, Socket.io), Git(Bitbucket)
STREAMING SERVICE WEB-APPLICATION "TVPLUS"	
Company:	ООО "Медиатек"
Company Location:	Belarus, Minsk
Project Industry:	Video streaming service
Project Web Site:	<u>tvplus.by</u>
Project Location:	Belarus
Description	Create a responsive web app based on the created Api with the ability to authorize and purchase content for Life subscribers.
	Users can:
	View videos and TV channels.
	Buy subscriptions and content.
	Configure the application.
	Search and filter content.
Position:	Front-end developer
Overall Team Size:	1 front-end developer, 1 QA engineer, 1 designer, 1 manager
Tools & Technologies:	React (Next.js, Redux, Material-UI, shaka-player) Git(GitLab)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Company:	Маркетинговое агенство "Чеширский Кот"
Company Location / web:	Minsk, <u>cheshire-cat.by</u>
Duration:	September 2019 – present time
Position:	Middle Front-end developer
Responsibilities:	 Development of software solutions for the needs of customers. Development Frontend part of platform using any frameworks. Use markup languages like HTML to create user-friendly web pages Maintain and improve website Write functional requirement documents and guides. Help back-end developers with coding and troubleshooting
Tools & Technologies:	HTML / CSS / JS (native / JQuery/ TypeScript), Angular 8-9 React/Redux Next.js Webpack Node.js (Express, Mongoose) CMS 1C-Bitrix
Company:	Freelance
Company Location:	Minsk
Duration:	May 2017 — September 2019
Position:	Front-end developer
Responsibilities:	 Development of software solutions for the needs of customers. Development Frontend part of platform using Angular framework. Use markup languages like HTML to create user-friendly web pages
Tools & Technologies:	HTML / CSS / JS (native / TypeScript) Angular 8 Webpack Node.js (Express, Mongoose)
Company:	Online shop carcam.by
Company Location:	Minsk
Duration:	March 2012 — February 2013
Position:	Web-developer/Co-founderCreation and development of online shop.
Responsibilities:	Maintain and improve online shop.
Tools & Technologies:	HTML / CSS / JS CMS Joomla PHP
Company:	ООО "Белкарпластик"
Company Location:	Minsk, <u>bcpl.by</u>
Duration:	April 2008 — December 2015
Position:	CNC Operator Programmer
Responsibilities:	 Use CAD/CAM software to create CNC programs Setup and run Multi Axis CNC Vertical Mills Perform and coordinate preventive maintenance activities on equipment and tooling Also my responsibilities included 3D modeling, CAD/CAM design, and I had experience in teaching and staff training.
Tools & Technologies:	UNIGRAPHICS NX